Let your attention settle.
Keep your spine straight,
your shoulders open.
Relax your body.
Feel your head,
your shoulders,
your arms.
Feel the pressure of
your body on the cushion.
Feel your hands at their points of contact.
Be aware of your breathing,
moment after moment.
Notice the contact of the body:
feet,
back,
hands.
Sensations arise on their
own… and change on their own.
Just let experience be as it is.
Simply rest here,
aware of
being a body,
breathing,
present.
Notice if there is a quality of
awareness that is already here,
even before you think about it.
If you notice it, just let
your attention stay there.
Don't try to hold it.
Don't try to push it away.